http://drumsplayerworld.com/about/privacy-statement/

HomePrivacy Statement Privacy Statement
At DrumsPlayerWorld.com, we understand the need to protect the privacy of your online users. This set of guidelines had been created to show you how any personal information of our online visitors are collected and used.
1. Personal Information You Might Choose to Provide
On our website, we run a weekly newsletter that provides free lessons and drumming related information for people who sign up. During the sign up process, you would be required to provide us with your name and email address. In accordance to the CAN-SPAM act, each of our newsletters contain links that allow you to unsubscribe at any point.
If you no longer want to receive any future messages, simply look for the unsubscribe link. By clicking the unsubscribe link, you will be immediately taken off our mailing list.
Sometimes, you might choose to communicate with us through the email for questions or advice on specific topics. Do note that we may retain the content of the email for our own reference and housekeeping purposes.
2. Website Use Information
Like many other websites, DrumsPlayerWorld.com uses a standard technology called cookies to help track and collect information on how our visitors are engaging in our website. In essence, a cookie is an anonymous identifier for a web visitor. It contains information that can help us tailor made or customize the website settings to your personal preferences.
Rest assured that cookies do not allow us to gather any personal or sensitive information about you. It is used purely as a means to help us improve the site experience for you.
3. Sharing and Selling Information
We will never share or sell any kind of information (such as names and email addresses) to any 3rd party sources. Your privacy is 100% safe with us.
Your Consent
By using our website, you will automatically agree to and consent to our collection and use of your personal info according to what was described above. At any point in time, we may choose to update or make any changes to the existing policies. We reserve the right to do this without any notice to. Please e-mail any questions, concerns or comments you have about our Privacy Statement to admin [[[[[@]]]]]] drumsplayerworld.com.
Related Articles
The Benefits of the Moeller Method And What It Can DoPicking Up Rhythms By Ear And Processing ThemMoeller Method Strokes And TricksHow to Select Proper Drum Sticks From the Music Store
We Recommend…
More On-Topic LessonsContact Us
Submit a Lesson!
Terms Of Use
Privacy
FTC Disclosure
Our Exclusive Newsletter!
Recent CommentsMichael Aubrecht on Drum Lessons For KidsCansu on Articles And General Topicsdjtbird on Go Go Rhythms And Patterns to Have Fun Withrattler on Warm Up Exercises to Get Your Body Ready For Drumming
Be Social. Join Us!
Tweet
About Dennis McCord I had been an avid drummer ever since my dad taught me how to play the drums at an age of 18 from my basement. This website is created to provide a free resource for would-be drummers.
Other LinksContact Us
Submit a Lesson!
Terms Of Use
Privacy
FTC Disclosure
DrumsPlayerWorld.com © Copyright 2014 | Dennis McCord Productions
